仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
原创翻译  双语字幕
人人影视
YYeTs.com
翻译：豆包  奈奈  Iz
校对：Iz          总监   Iz
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第八集
时间轴：function        后期：吉吉
还记得我昨晚放的那个屁吗
Hey, remember my fart from last night?
说详细些
Be more specific.
也许这声音能让你们想起来
Maybe this will ring a bell.
我想起来了
Oh, yeah.
我教它要爱国
I taught it to love its country.
这首叫"乱弹琴"
It's "Stankee Doodle Dandy."
酷  再弹首别的
Cool. Play something else.
弹生日歌吧
Play "Happy Birthday"
快到我生日了
'cause my birthday's coming up.
来一首生日快乐版的"乱弹琴"
Play "Happy Stankee Birthday."
弹啊  弹啊
Do it. Do it.
肯定有意思  弹啊
It'll be funny. Do it.
考特尼  我看你该吃药了
Hey, Courtney, take a chill pill.
天哪
Oh, my gosh.
不  没关系  不  各位  各位
Uh... No, it's all right. No, guys, guys.
我会吃的  我会的
I will take a chill pill, I will.
我本来就有先天性心脏病
Because I have a congenital heart condition,
每天都得吃药
and I take them every day.
-我得过一次疱疹  -我腿上有伤口
- I had shingles once. - I have a cut on my leg.
那可都不是先天性的
Those things aren't congenital.
表演结束了
Show's over.
我们到课堂上讨论"先天性"的问题吧
We got to get our congenitals to class.
嗨  琳
Hi, Lin.
嗨  格雷琴
Hey, Gretchen.
你把这瓶水落美容院了
Just came by to return this bottle
我是来还你的
of water you left at the salon.
什么时候的事
When did I leave that there?
两周前
Two weeks ago.
你们有失物招领处吗
Hey, do you guys have a lost and found?
有  怎么啦  你丢什么了
Yeah. Why? What'd you lose?
15磅  看看我
15 pounds. Look at me.
真的  你瘦了
Oh, yeah, you lost weight.
真棒
Good for you.
你减肥的秘决是什么  格雷琴
Wow, what's your secret, Gretchen?
我用了皮皮减肥法
I went on the Skin Deep diet.
只能吃水果和蔬菜皮
You can only eat fruits and vegetable skins,
体重自然就掉下来了
and the weight just fell right off.
有一次  我不小心吃了一根香蕉皮
One time, I accidentally ate a banana peel,
但之后好像没有达到你这样的效果
but I didn't look like you afterwards.
我得走了
Well, I got to run.
格雷琴
Hey, Gretchen.
你看起来很不错啊
Wow, you look great.
你是减肥了吗
Did you lose weight?
减了点  看
Little bit. Look--
我的纹身都不像以前那样被撑变形了
my tattoo's not stretched out anymore.
-几乎像一只普通的海豚了  -还真是
- It almost looks like a regular dolphin. - Wow, yeah.
看看我大腿上的纹身吧  鲍鲍
Look at my thigh tattoo, Bobby.
我把短裤卷上去
Oh, let me pull my shorts up here.
-不用看了  -行了  可以了
- It's okay. - Okay. All right.
-再见  格雷琴  -再见  各位
- Bye, Gretchen. - Bye, everybody.
再见
Bye.
你的身材看起来刚刚好
You're perfect the way you are.
一磅都别再减了
Don't lose one more pound.
我不会的  也许吧  我也不确定
I won't, probably. I don't know.
格雷琴看上去很不错  是吧
Gretchen looks good, huh?
是啊  还行吧
Yeah, I guess she looks all right.
你的眼角怎么在抽搐
Why is your eye twitching?
因为我很为她感到高兴
Because I'm very happy for her.
人家现在是性感女郎
So what if she's the hot one now,
我却戴着游泳圈  那又怎样
and I'm the one with the muffin top.
得了  琳  你很漂亮
Oh, come on, Lin, you look great.
我喜欢你的游泳圈
I like your muffin top.
-这么说你认为我有游泳圈咯  -啥
- So you think I have a muffin top? - What?
不  不  我是说  没有
No, no, I said... No.
我也要减肥  鲍勃
I'm going on that diet, Bob, and when I'm done,
到时候我会变得和格雷琴的姐姐一样瘦
I'm gonna look like Gretchen's skinny sister.
琳  格蕾琴的姐姐确实很瘦
Gretchen's sister is skinny, Lin,
但那是因为她吸毒
but it's because she's on methamphetamines.
有效果就行  泰迪  别指指点点
Whatever works, Teddy. Don't judge!
如果你们打算插队  就别痴心妄想了
If you guys are trying to cut the line, forget it.
连尼帮我们占了队
Lenny's giving us backwards cuts.
占队
Backwards cuts?
他们发现了一个漏洞
They found a loophole.
吉恩  你猜怎么着
Hey, Gene, guess what?
怎么了  鲁帕
What, Rupa?
我知道有人喜欢你哦
I know someone who likes you.
是连尼吗
Is it Lenny?
我也想有人帮我占队
'Cause I want backwards cuts.
我想她的意思是有人"暧暧"你
I think she means someone like-likes you.
是学校的护士吗
Is it the school nurse?
她说过我的体温相当正常
She said I was the perfect temperature.
我可不能告诉你
Can't tell you.
这是个秘密
It's a secret.
看来我们永远都不会知道了
Aw, I guess we'll never know now.
不管是谁  希望她觉得我这招很厉害
Well, whoever she is, I hope she appreciates that I can do this.
我真不明白
I don't get it.
我这么努力  结果倒有人暗恋他
I try and try and he ends up with the secret crush.
可能是你太努力了  女朋友
Maybe don't try so hard, girlfriend.
好吧  我明白你的意思了
Okay, I see your point.
你觉得"暧暧"吉恩的是谁
Who do you think like-likes Gene?
"青春期  青春期  青春期"
"Puberty, puberty, puberty."
你们的对话只能让我联想到这个
That's all I hear when you guys talk.
但我们是他的姐妹
But we're his sisters.
要是我们对她不满意呢
What if we don't approve of her?
挑别人毛病我最爱了
Oh, judging people.
既然你这么说的话
Well, when you put it like that...
发质差  有口臭  脾气坏
Bad hair, bad breath, bad attitude,
眼睛  鼻子  嘴巴  仪态
eyes, nose, mouth, posture...
所以不会是莎拉  温迪和莉琪
So, we know it's not Sarah, Wendy or Lizzie.
也许是朱莉
Maybe it's Julie?
不是她  她"暧暧"连尼・戴斯特法诺
Nah, she like-likes Lenny Destefano.
老天  怎么都喜欢连尼・戴斯特法诺
Geez, who isn't on the Lenny Destefano train.
也太抢手了吧
It sold out even before it left the station.
鲁帕呢
What about Rupa?
也许她告诉我们
Maybe she told us
暗恋的秘密是卖关子呢
about the secret crush to throw us off her trail?
不会  鲁帕没那么聪明
No. Rupa's not that smart.
她以为弯管通心粉真是用胳膊肘做的
She thought elbow macaroni was made of elbows.
弯管通心粉的英文说法中有"胳膊肘"一词
那可的确不对
Oh, and that's not true.
也许是我们没想到的人
Maybe it's someone we're not thinking of.
考特尼・惠勒
Courtney Wheeler!
吉恩
Hi, Gene.
我听说好像有人"暧暧"你
I heard somebody like-likes you.
你知道是谁吗
Do you know who it is?
不知道
Nope.
她和你同年级
She's in your grade,
觉得你非常可爱
and she thinks you're really cute.
她有一头金发
And she has blond hair.
她正看着你呢
And she's looking right at you.
就是我
It's me!
天哪
Oh, boy.
你也"暧暧"考特尼吗
So, do you like-like Courtney?
你想和她约会吗
Do you want to go out with her?
说想  说想  说想
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
你"暧暧"她  对吧
You like-like her, right?
说是
Yes.
我想是吧
I guess?
天哪  真不敢相信  但他的确说是了
Oh, my God, I can't believe he said yes, But he did.
你们去约会吧
You guys are going out.
来做个爱的标记吧
Let's make it official.
这代表一辈子吗
Is this forever?
对  我忘了
Oh right, I forgot.
吉恩・贝尔彻  考特尼・惠勒  永远
不
Oh, no.
好了
There it is.
都  写下来了
It's all, eh, written down.
好吧  谢谢
All right. Well, thank you.
沼泽港天主教学校还有个名额
Bog Harbor Catholic has an opening.
你只需要穿裙子去说你叫尤金伲亚就行了
You'll just need to wear a skirt and go by the name Eugenia.
露易丝  你说什么呢
Louise, what are you talking about?
吉恩正在换学校
Gene's switching schools.
吉恩  你为什么想换学校
Gene, why do you want to switch schools?
有人欺负你吗
Are you being bullied?
谁伤了我的小宝贝
Who's hurting my baby boy?
我倒希望我受欺负了
I wish I had a bully.
事实比这糟得多
This is way worse.
考特尼・威尔"暧暧"他
Courtney Wheeler like-likes him.
考特尼问吉恩是否想和她约会
Courtney asked Gene if he wanted to go out with her,
他答应了
and he said yes.
好呀  吉恩  你也开始约会了
All right, Gene, you're on the board.
干得好
Way to go.
有人要约会了哦
I hear dating bells.
谁是考特尼
So, who's Courtney?
考特尼・惠勒是我们年级最烦人的女孩
Courtney Wheeler is the most annoying girl in my grade.
-在学校也是  -在全天下都是
- In school. - In the world.
她到底有什么问题
Oh, well, what's so bad about her?
她话太多  呼吸声太吵
She talks too much, she breathes too loud,
嘴里还万年都含着她那条项链
and she's always sucking on her necklace.
她的口气有汗臭味
And her breath smells like sweat.
她喜欢在上厕所的时候打电话
Yeah, and she talks on her phone when she goes to the bathroom.
让别人会错意
It's confusing.
嗨  最近怎么样
Hey, how's it going?
很好  多谢关心
Good. Thanks for asking.
我在厕所呢  你呢
I'm in the bathroom. Where are you?
我也在厕所
I'm in the bathroom, too.
很明显嘛
I thought you knew that.
不好意思  先等一下
Sorry, hold on.
有人以为我在跟她讲话呢
Some girl thinks I'm talking to her.
叫她少管闲事  我等着
Oh, well get rid of her. I'll wait here.
吉恩  那你为什么还要答应和她约会呢
Gene, then why did you say you'd go out with her?
大家都看着我呢
Her friends were staring at me!
别人会把我当混蛋的  老爸
I didn't want to be a jerk, Dad.
如果你真的不喜欢她就不算混蛋啊
Well, you're not being a jerk if you don't like her.
-是不"暧暧"她  -不"暧暧"她
- Like-like her. - Like-like her.
你父亲说得没错  吉恩
Your father's right, Gene.
老妈什么时候开始吃垃圾了
When did Mom start eating garbage?
这是土豆皮
These are potato peels.
这是皮皮减肥法
I'm on the Skin Deep diet.
我只能吃果皮和蔬菜皮
I'm only allowed to eat fruit and vegetable skins.
可好吃了
It's delicious.
你要知道  拖得越久
You know, the longer you wait,
就越难说出你的真实想法
the harder it's gonna be to tell her how you really feel.
是么  那你要什么时候
Oh, yeah? When are you gonna
对老妈说出你的真实想法
tell Mom how you really feel?
他说什么
What'd he say?
你好  吉恩
Hi, Gene.
-你好  考特尼  -好可爱哦
- Hi, Courtney. - Aww. So cute.
我们应该一起走进学校
We're walking into school together.
你懂的  因为我们在约会嘛
'Cause, you know, now we're going out.
牵着我的手
Take my hand.
要知道跟我牵手
You should know when you hold hands with me,
就意味着跟我吃过的所有食物牵手了哦
you hold hands with everything I've ever eaten.
粘糊糊的更好
I don't care if they're sticky.
这样才不容易分开嘛
Just makes them harder to pull apart.
好可爱哦
So cute.
简直难以置信
Unbelievable.
各位  我们进去咯
You guys, we're going in.
你知道打我头上的哪个部位能让我失忆吗
Do you know where to hit me on my head to give me amnesia?
这吗  我是谁
Right here. Who am I?
蒂娜  再试试
Tina, try again.
我是谁
Who am I?
蒂娜  再试试
Tina, try again.
我是谁
Who am I?
蒂娜  使点儿劲
Tina, harder!
*我们一起手牵手*
*We go together*
一天零五个半小时纪念日快乐
*一起到白头*
*Remembered forever*
*这是注定的相会*
*That's the way it should be*
*我们是天生一对*
*We're one of a kind Yech!*
*我俩的誓言永不碎*
*Our names are signed*
老妈  你确定要吃
Mom, a whole cantaloupe skin?
一整块哈密瓜皮吗
You sure?
这是我该得的
I earned it.
我晚饭就只吃了猕猴桃外面那层毛
All I had for breakfast was kiwi fuzz.
口感就像是在舔你老爸的背一样
It was like licking your father's back. Ugh.
-谢谢  琳  -咋了
- Thanks, Lin. - What?
吉恩  也就是说
Gene, let me get this straight.
我现在要载你去和一个你并不喜欢
I'm driving you on a date with a girl
早就该分手的女孩约会
who you don't like and should've broken up with by now?
-是不"暧暧"  -蒂娜  我知道
- Like-like. - Tina, I know.
其实是四人约会
Actually, it's a double date.
朱莉和连尼・戴斯特法诺也参加
Julie and Lenny Destefano are coming.
朱莉最好别太迷恋连尼
Julie better not get too attached to Lenny.
我可不愿她毁了这匹种马
That is one stallion that won't be broken.
给  老爸  你可能会需要耳塞
Here, Dad, you'll probably need ear plugs.
如果还不顶用的话
And if those aren't enough,
用这个敲自己脑袋
hit yourself over the head with this.
她也没那么糟吧  露易丝
I'm sure she's not that bad, Louise.
-貌似有  -那你就错了
- Hmm... she kind of is. - Ehh... you would be wrong.
准备好大吃一惊吧
Prepare to be surprised.
老爸  拿着  拿着
Dad, take it, take it.
就当我送你了  拿着吧
I don't even need it back, just take it.
-再见  -等你四处找商店买锤子
- Good-bye. All right, well, good luck finding
可别怪我没提醒你
a drive-thru hammer store.
踢  踢  踢
Kick, kick, kick.
考特尼  能不踢我的座位吗
Courtney, will you stop kicking the seat?
我没踢  踢
I'm not kicking. Kick.
是吗  但我能感觉到
Really? I can feel it.
而且你还边踢边说"踢"
And you're saying kick.
不  不是我  踢
No. It's not me. Kick.
朱莉坐得远
Well, Julie's too far away.
又不是连尼
And it's not Lenny.
我没踢  鲍勃先生
Not me, Mr. B.
我知道  连尼
Oh, I know, Lenny.
也许只是你的幻想  踢
Maybe you're just imagining it. Kick.
感觉到了吗
Did you feel that?
-感觉到了  -踢
- Yes. - Kick.
这下呢
How about that?
考特尼  拜托
Courtney, please.
考特尼不能控制自己的腿
Courtney can't control her legs
因为她有先天性心脏病
because she has a congenital heart condition.
这两者有什么关系
What do those things have to do with each other?
世间万物都没关系
What does anything have to do with each other?
我的天
Oh, my God.
-吉恩  -干嘛
- Gene. - What?
-她太讨厌了  -我知道
- She's so annoying. - I know.
-你必须得跟她分手  -我知道
- You have to break up with her. - I know.
回车里来  我们可以直接闪人
Get back in the car. We can drive away.
-真的吗  -我看行
- Seriously? - I think so.
算了  算了  太晚了  她来了
Forget it, forget it. It's too late. Here she comes.
我不知道要怎么跟他分手  老爸
I don't know how to break up with her, Dad.
你就  你好  考特尼
Just.... Oh hi, Courtney.
我们在聊天
We were just talking.
闲聊而已
Just chatting.
来吧  吉恩  我们走  来嘛
Come on, Gene, let's go, come on!
我想再跟我爸说两句
I just want to finish these chats with Dad.
老爸  我要再跟你说两句
Dad, I just want to chat with you some more.
我们得去占后排的座位
We have to go get seats in the back row
不知道为什么总有人抱怨我嚼东西的方式
'cause people complain about the way I chew for some reason.
吉恩  老爸对不住你了
Gene, I'm so sorry.
我想跟考特尼分手
I want to break up with Courtney,
但太难了
but it's so hard.
我的人生比地球上任何人都艰难
My life is more difficult than anyone else's on the planet,
没错  包括那些饥饿儿童  别问了
and, yes, I'm including starving children, so don't ask.
我们来练习练习吧
Why don't we practice?
蒂娜  你当考特尼
Tina, you be Courtney.
吉恩  跟她分手
Gene, break up with her.
去吧  你可以的
Go ahead, you can do it.
考特尼  我们分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
好吧
Oh, okay.
请不要难过
Please don't be sad.
不  我明白
No, I get it.
没关系
It's fine.
或许我们本来就不合适
It wouldn't have worked anyway.
太难了  我看还是等我们念不同的大学
This is so hard! Can't I just wait
再很自然地失去联系好了
till we go to different colleges and lose touch?
你做得很好  你做得很好
You're doing good. You're doing good.
来  跟我试试
Come on, try it with me.
考特尼  我们分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
什么  永远别想跟我分手
What?! You'll never break up with me!
因为我会先杀了你
I will kill you first!
算了
Forget it.
-我不干了  -不行  再来
- I'm not doing it. - Yes, you are. Again!
考特尼  我们分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
-不要  -再来
- Nooooo! - Again!
我们分手吧
I think we should break up.
三小时后
考特尼  我们分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
-我懂的  -再来
- I understand. - Again.
考特尼  我们分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
你合格了
You're ready.
我们分手吧
I think we should break up.
我们分手吧  我们分手吧
I think we should break up. I think we should break up.
我们不需要
We don't want any.
那好  再见
Okay, bye.
等等  等一下
Hold on, wait a second.
我跟你闹着玩呢  别当真
I'm kidding. That was a joke.
有什么我能帮你的吗
What can I do for you?
这是考特尼的家吗
Is Courtney home?
你是哪位
Who's asking?
我是吉恩
I'm Gene.
你就是传说中的吉恩啊
Oh, so you're the famous Gene.
进来说吧  大名鼎鼎的吉恩
Come on in, famous Gene.
那  好吧
Uh... okay.
考特尼
Courtney!
稍等  她在楼上  得大声喊才行
Hold on, I'm yell... You got to yell up the stairs.
要不她听不见  吉恩来了  小考
She can't hear me. Gene's down here, Court!
我在吃药  老爸
I'm taking my pill, Daddy.
跟他说我一会就下来
Tell him I'll be down in a second.
她在吃药  一会就下来
Okay, she's taking her pill. She's gonna be down...
你都听见了是吧
You probably heard that, didn't you?
跟我来
Follow me.
你从哪儿弄来这些的
Where did you get all this stuff?
你父母给你买的吗
Did your parents buy it for you?
对  就是他们买的
Yup, they did.
你喜欢吗
You like that?
别客气  你想怎么弹怎么弹
Go ahead. Go nuts.
你为什么会有这些玩意
Why do you have all this?
你是莫比[美国歌手]吗
Are you Moby?
不是
No.
莫比谈不上  不过也算是音乐圈的人
I'm not Moby, but I am in the music business.
我也是音乐圈的
I'm in the music business!
是吗
Is that right?
我主要写广告歌
Well, I write jingles.
现在我在写嘟嘟薯条的广告歌
Right now, I'm working on one for Pips potato chips.
嘟嘟薯条声声脆
Pop in a Pips-- Pop! Potato chips
嘎吱嘎吱
Crunch!
真好听
That's beautiful.
我以前从没见过艺术家真人
I've never met a real artist before.
吉恩  既然你是考特尼的新朋友
Well, Gene, now that you're Courtney's new friend,
你随时可以来这个乐器天堂
you got an all-access pass to gear heaven!
我的天
Oh, my God!
乐器天堂
Gear heaven!
吉恩
Hey, Gene.
莫比
Moby?!
吉恩  吉恩
Hey, Gene... Gene!
你过来是有什么事要跟我说吗
What'd you come over here to tell me?
那个
Um, well...
爆炸咯
Ooh! Explosion!
什么事
What is it?
我就想告诉你我好像"暧暧暧"上你了
I just wanted to tell you that I like-like-like you!
真  真的吗
Wha-wha-really?
我的天
Oh, my God!
老爸
Daddy...
吉恩和考特尼坐树上
Gene and Courtney sitting in a tree...
坐呀嘛坐树上
S-I-t-t-I-n-g!
我能搞定的
I can make this work!
他回来了
He's back.
-分手成功了吗  -没  比那更好
- Did you break up with Courtney? - No! Better!
还能有什么更好的呢
What could be better than that?
我见过她的潮爸了
I met her cool dad.
你个无知的蠢货
Oh, you weak idiot!
露易丝  别闹
Louise, stop it.
搞什么搞  吉恩  你脑子进水了吗
Seriously, Gene, what's wrong with you?
考特尼她爸是写广告歌的
Courtney's dad writes jingles.
记得凤爪猫肠不
Remember Pawsage's Cat Sausages?
啊对  我记起来了
Oh, yeah! I remember that.
凤爪猫肠  肠中的极品  喵
Pawsages are pawsitively purrfect! Meow!
听了就觉得饿
Ooh! That just made me hungry.
天哪  琳达  我拜托你吃点东西
God, Linda, just eat something.
不要
No!
考特尼要在这周末开生日派对
Courtney's having a birthday party this weekend,
特大好消息  我们全家都被邀请了
and great news-- I got us all on the list.
真好啊  我们都被邀请了
Ooh! We're on the list!
没错  小胃胃  也请你了呢
That's right, tummy. You're coming, too.
你说什么  小胃胃
What's that, tummy?
不行不行  你不能吃冰激凌
No, you can't have ice cream.
别算上我
Count me out.
行  那你就看不到我的表演了
Fine! Then you'll miss my performance.
什么表演
What performance?
我会写首广告歌
I'm gonna write a jingle
在派对上演唱
and sing it at the party.
道格听到了
When Doug hears it,
一定会和我签唱片合约
he's gonna give me a record deal!
广告歌合约吧
A jingle deal.
她爸爸才不会跟你签什么合约  吉恩
Her dad isn't gonna give you a record deal, Gene.
他会的
Yes, he is!
那你也不能就因为她爸爸
You can't keep going out with Courtney,
而和考特尼在一起
just because of her dad.
就是  你都不"暧暧"她
Yeah, you don't even like-like her.
才不是  我觉得现在有点"暧暧"她了
No, I think I might like-like her now.
不  你没有
No, you don't.
你真的没有  宝贝
Nah, you don't, honey.
你说句人话成吗
Why don't you try speaking in words,
我真受够了你张嘴就放屁
instead of your damn dirty lies!
我没开玩笑  我觉得我会的
Seriously! I think I do!
只要闭上双眼  捂住耳朵
When I shut my eyes and cover my ears,
我就觉得我还是能和她过一辈子的
I feel like I maybe could spend the rest of my life with her.
我意思是  "这样啊"
I mean, "Oh."
吉恩呢
Where's Gene?
他在考特尼家勾引她爸呢
Oh, he's at Courtney's, hitting on her dad.
琳  你看看烤架上的汉堡好了没
Hey, Lin, can you check the burgers on the grill for me?
鲍勃  我现在不能接近食物
I can't be around food right now, Bob.
你难道没意识到自己是开餐厅的吗
You do realize you work in a restaurant, right?
别跟我提餐厅  听见我就饿
Don't say restaurant; it makes me hungry.
你还好吧  琳达
You okay, Linda?
我妈这么古怪都因为
Mom's cranky because she's only had
这三天她就光啃蔬果皮了
fruit and vegetable skins for three days.
你是琳达吗  不是就别插嘴
Is your name Linda? I don't think so!
对不起  宝贝
I'm sorry, honey.
过来  对不起
Come here; I'm sorry.
过来
Come here.
-过来抱我  -好吧
- Come hug Mommy! - Okay.
让妈妈抱抱
Mommy hug.
你用的可可油洗发水吗
Mm! Did you use that cocoa butter shampoo?
是的
Yeah.
油...油...油
Bu... bu... bu...
-黄油  黄油  -琳  琳
- Butter... butter... - Lin... Lin...
干嘛  干嘛
What? What?
别吃蒂娜的头发
Stop eating Tina's hair.
老爸  我为你写了首广告歌
Dad, I made up a jingle for you.
-你想听听吗  -不太想
- You want to hear it? - Not really.
让你请客有脸面
Have a feast for your face
就来光头鲍勃的汉堡店
Have a burger at Bald Bob's!
前面还不错  秃鲍勃那就差了
It was pretty good, up until you said Bald Bob.
道格说写广告歌要押韵
Doug says when you write a jingle, use alliteration.
又受教了  广而告之教授
Oh, thanks for the lesson, Professor Jingleberry.
好样的
Good one.
莫特  我也为你作了一首
I've got one for you, too, Mort.
如果有人死翘翘
If you got yourself a stiff
千万别往沟里倒
Don't dump it in a ditch
快快来把莫特找
Take your corpse to Mort!
就是我
That's me!
还有点才气  你听这个呢
That was really good. How about this one?
苦口婆心劝分手
Told you to break up with Courtney
你却偏偏不回头
And you didn't listen
永远要把苦来受
And now you're stuck with her forever
自食其果才罢休
So suck it!
这个有点难记  不过可以试试看
That's not very catchy, but we'll work on it.
考特尼生日快乐
我觉得头晕
I feel light-headed.
我完全没感觉
I'm not feeling anything.
这批货肯定被掺水了
I think somebody stepped on this batch.
蛋糕有人要吗
Cake, anyone?
别给我  我在减肥
Not for me, I'm on a diet.
鲍勃  鲍勃  去拿块蛋糕
Bob! Bob! Take a piece of cake!
我不想吃
I don't want cake.
就拿一块
Just take a piece.
我想近距离看看它
I want to look at it, up-close.
好吧
Fine.
酥皮也算是蛋糕的一种皮吧
Oh, icing's like cake skin, right?
什么
What?!
琳  你控制着点
Lin, get ahold of yourself.
好吧  那我离你远点
Okay, I'm walking away from you now.
鲍勃  我听说你是做汉堡的
So, Bob, I hear you're a burger man.
没错  吉恩说过你是写广告歌的
Yep. Gene mentioned that you write jingles.
你现在是不是跟我想到一块儿去了
You thinking what I'm thinking?
恐怕没有
I'm afraid to say yes.
滋滋牛排和大块面包
Blazin' beef and big old buns
幸会
Well, nice meeting you.
安静  各位
Attention, everybody.
往这边看  派对主人公要发言了
Look at me! Birthday girl talking!
请到这边来
Come on, everyone!
他们真般配  对吧
They make a cute couple, huh?
他们  只是站在一起而已
They certainly are standing next to each other.
贝尔彻先生  我不是让安静了吗
Mr. Belcher! I said attention!
是他先说的
He talked first, so...
他先问我的
Well, he asked me a question.
我才没有
No... I didn't.
反正你也说了
Well, you did, too.
算了  总之
Um, okay, anyway,
吉恩给我写了一首爱的广告歌
Gene's written a love jingle about me,
现在要为大家表演
and he's gonna perform it now.
准确点说  其实是加长版的广告歌小样
This is more of an extended jingle jam/demo reel.
我把它叫做"沉默的爱"
I call it "Silent Love."
当我闭上双眼  捂住耳朵
When I close my eyes and I cover my ears
仿佛感觉你不曾来过
It's almost like you aren't here
这就是沉默的爱
It's a silent love-- shh!
沉默的爱
Silent love!
Silent love.
不  别出声
No, seriously-- shh!
这就是沉默的爱
Talkin' 'bout silent love!
别唱了
Stop singing!
所有女士请跟我一起唱  沉默的爱
All the ladies in the house now: silent love!
沉默的爱
Silent love?
吉恩
Gene!
我还没叫男士呢
I have to do the fellas in the house!
怎么能光叫女士不叫男士呢
You can't do the ladies and not do the fellas!
-你给我安静  -我要唱
- Just be quiet! - Let me sing!
不行  这不是男女对唱歌
No! It's not a duet!
沉默的爱  这就是沉
Silent love... it's a silent...
你烦死了
You are so annoying!
什么
What?
别唱了  别说话
Just stop singing! Stop talking!
别呼吸
Stop breathing!
我是不是把她的生日搞砸了
Do you think I've ruined her birthday?
你说得对  老爸
You were right, Dad.
我早就该跟考特尼分手了
I should've broken up with Courtney a long time ago.
现在我害死了她
Now I've killed her.
你没害死考特尼  吉恩
You didn't kill Courtney, Gene.
是啊  宝贝儿  她会没事的
Yeah, honey, she'll be okay.
我想的话
Probably.
往好的方面想嘛
Look at the bright side:
这样你就永远省去和女孩儿约会的麻烦了
You'll never have to go out with any girls again,
因为大家都讨厌你
because they all hate you.
他们讨厌我  道格讨厌我
They hate me, Doug hates me...
连尼讨厌你
Lenny hates you.
我的事业给毁了
My career is ruined.
吉恩  道格不会跟你签唱片合约的
Gene, Doug wasn't gonna give you a record deal.
他压根儿就不做唱片
He doesn't even give out record deals.
他没那个本事
He doesn't have that power.
-他有  -他没有
- Yes, he does! - No, he doesn't.
你对音乐圈一无所知
You don't know anything about the music business.
看  医生过来了
Look, the doctor's coming over.
蒂娜  你还在吸氦气吗
Tina, are you still doing helium?
-没有啊  -蒂娜
- No... - Tina!
-我喜欢嘛  -给我来点
- I like it. - Give me some.
吉恩
Gene...
你要去看看她吗
would you like to see her now?
不用了
Uh, I'm good.
再不去就没机会了
Now's the time.
老爸  我要跟她讲什么
Dad, what do I say to her?
就随便聊点轻松的话题
Just make light small talk.
没错  让她振作起来
Yeah, cheer her up.
做几个放屁的声音逗她笑笑
Make some fart noises, huh?
这会儿我恐怕做不出来
I don't think I have it in me.
原来可以
Oh! I do!
去吧
There he is.
吉恩  是你吗
Gene, is that you?
是我
Yes.
帮  帮我把项链放嘴里
P... Put my necklace in my mouth?
你说的那些话是真心的吗
Did you really mean those things that you said?
不是
No!
好吧  有一部分是
Well, a little bit.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这么说你不"暧暧"我咯
So, you don't like-like me?
是的  但是  我喜欢跟你有关的东西
No, but... I like things about you.
例如你老爸  和他的东西
Like your dad and his stuff.
你在利用我
You were using me.
我觉得用"建立关系网"这个说法更合适
I prefer the term "Networking."
吉恩  你要是想跟我分手  就说吧
Gene, if you're gonna break up with me, break up with me.
我受得了
I can take it.
考特尼  我想我们还是分手吧
Courtney, I think we should break up.
我的天哪  考特尼
Oh, my God! Courtney!
医生  救命呀
Doctor, do something!
我们已经无计可施了
There's nothing we can do.
你伤了她的心
You broke her heart.
逗你玩的
Psych!
干得漂亮  考特尼
Way to go, Courtney.
你没事吗
You're okay?
没事
Yeah.
你一直在演戏吗
Did you fake this whole thing?
不
No.
心悸是真的  不过已经稳定下来了
The palpitations were real, but we stabilized her.
谢谢  齐格勒医生
Thanks, Dr. Chegler.
不客气
Oh, you're welcome.
你真该看看自己刚才那张脸
You should've seen your face.
你看见他的脸了没
Did you see his face?
很有意思
It was very funny.
你吓到我了
You scared me!
你对我做了那样的事
I think you kind of deserved it,
这难道不是你应得的吗
after what you did to me.
你说的对
I guess you're right.
没事了  我原谅你
It's okay. I'll forgive you.
条件是你要让彼得・派斯卡德罗跟我约会
If you get Peter Pescadero to go out with me.
彼得有部分听力障碍
Peter's got partial hearing loss.
你们太配了
It's a perfect match.
还要帮我洗便壶
And if you clean my bedpan.
很公平
Fair enough.
道格  我还能去你的乐器天堂吗
Doug, can I still visit you in gear heaven?
不行  乐器地狱都不行  吉恩
Nope. Not a chance in gear hell, Gene.
好吧
Okeydokey.
什么嘛  一点都没轻
What the hell? I didn't lose a thing!
你穿着衣服呢  衣服还有点重量
You're wearing clothes; that adds a little weight.
对哦
You're right.
-你太聪明了  -是啊
- Oh, he's so smart. - Yeah.
琳  别别  别  琳达  别这样
Lin, no... no, no... Linda, stop.
琳  你怎么能在这儿脱衣服
Lin, you can't take off your clothes here!
鲍勃  我需要准确的数字
Bob, I need an accurate number!
琳  我看减肥快把你搞疯了
Lin, this diet is making you crazy.
让我脱下来
Just take it off...
你跟本就不需要减肥
You don't even need to be on it.
你看起来好得很
You look great.
可我有游泳圈啊
What about my muffin top?
你知道谁没有游泳圈吗
You know who doesn't have a muffin top?
坚持去健身
People who go to the gym all the time,
而且没孩子的人
and who don't have kids.
别怪到我们头上来  死胖子
Don't blame us, fatty!
很辣嘛
Lookin' good!
色鬼老爷爷
Aw! Horny little grandpa.
谢谢你  色鬼老爷爷
Thanks, horny little grandpa!
我学到教训了
Well, I learned my lesson.
永远别和你不"暧暧"的人约会
Never date someone you don't like-like.
就算这意味着你失去了一个签唱片的机会
Even if it means losing out on a record deal.
这才是我的乖孩子
That's my boy.
吉恩  你拿着个便壶干嘛
Gene, why are you holding a bedpan?
医生说我可以拿走
The doctor said I could have it.
我以后再也不用厕所了
I'm never using a toilet again!
土豆泥
Ooh, mashed potatoes.
琳  你去哪儿
Lin, where are you going?
回来
Hey, come back here!
现在我看到她的游泳圈了
Oh, yeah, now I see her muffin top.
给我
Give me that!
六个月后
当我闭上双眼  捂住耳朵
When I close my eyes and I cover my ears
仿佛感觉你不曾来过
It's almost like you aren't here
沉默的消音器
本周到制定地点便可一睹
为本歌献声的消音器先生的风采
这就是沉默的消音器
It's Silent Muffler-- shh!
是我的歌  是我的歌  道格
That's my song! That's my song! Doug!